

Phattanothai Pukham



Personal Information

Fluke
Military Status

Reservist

Date of Availaility

Immediately

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

Contect

Skills



EDUCATION

2012-2016 Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science

Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

GPA 3.21

2009-2016 Pali language

Wat Paknam Bhasicharoen

WORK EXPERIENCE

DRIVEN DIGTAL, WFH

2022 - 2023

Frontend Developer

• Created frontend to requirements (Nuxtjs, Vuejs)

FREELANCE, WFH

2022 - 2023

Software Developer

- Created frontend to requirements (Angular, Vuejs, Reactjs)
- Created backend api for the frontend (Nestjs,PHP)
- Designed and created database (Mysql)
- Integrate third party app e.g. PG PP Shobet

BE YOUR TECH, WFH

2022 - 2022

Software Developer

https://crm.bullsphere.com)

- Created frontend to requirements (Nextjs,PHP)
- Created backend api for the frontend (Nestjs,PHP)
- Designed and created database (Mysql)
- Integrate third party app e.g. MT4 MT5 cTrader

OTEN INNOVATION, WFH

2020 - 2022

Full Stack Developer

- Created frontend to requirements (Nextjs Reactjs)
- Create a Hybrid application (React Native)
- Created backend api for the frontend (Nodejs Expressjs)
- Designed and created database (Mysql Mongodb)
- Write technical documents (swagger)
- Integrate third party app
- Deployed on a cloud server

WORLD GPS TRACKER, Chiang Rai

2019 - 2020

Programme

http://wgtgps.net

- Created frontend to requirements (Angular, Vuejs, PHP)
- Create a hybrid mobile application (Ionic)
- Created backend api for the web frontend and mobile application (Nodejs, Expressjs, PHP)
- Designed and created database (Mysql, Postgresql, Mongodb)
- Write technical documents
- Write technical documents
- Integrate third party app e.g. dlt, scg, cpf

Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

2018 - 2019

E ABILITIES

Coding Nodejs, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, SQL, Python

Flask, Expressjs, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vuejs, React, Nextjs, Ionic, Nuxtjs, React Native, Bootstrap, Material Design, Tailwind CSS, Ant Design One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g. sexy, pg, sbobet, sms, email, line api, MT4 MT5 cTrader

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

Config Replication Master and Slave Server Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Infrastructure Nginx, Kubernetes, Docker, Kong Api Gateway, GCP, AWS

Tools Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana, Gather Town, Slack, CircleCI, GitlabCI, Netlify, Cloudflare, Prometheus, Grafana, gRPC,

RabbitMQ

Operation Systems Window7/10, Mac OS X, Ubuntu, Window Server

Research Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, ArgoCD, Jenkins, Apache Kafka, Terraform, Ansible, SonarQube

Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, .Net Core, FastAPI, Rust, Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Kotlin, SwiftUI, Unity, Facebook API,

WebRTC, WASM